SARA WAGNER

Phone: 360-989-4566 | Email: sara.wagner23q@gmail.com | Portfolio: swagner23q.github.io in linkedin.com/in/swagner23q 🚦 github.com/swagner23q

Profile

A devoted and passionate professional with an eagerness to create innovative web experiences and grow knowledge within code. Reliable and friendly, able to work with little oversight and collaborate in team environments. Exceptional interpersonal skills with efficient and effective communication with above and beyond work ethic. Flexible in job functions and can easily prioritize heavy workloads daily.

Areas of Expertise

- Translate design and protyping to code
- Responsive web design best practices
- UI design and development

- Wireframing and prototyping
- Extensive creative troubleshooting
- Comprehensive quality assurance

Technical Competencies

HTML5, CSS3, Sass, Pug(Jade), Stylus, Sitecore CMS, Javascript, Ember.js, jQuery, Foundation, Materialize, Bootstrap, Bourbon, Neat, Adobe XD CC, Sketch, Photoshop CC, Node.js, Git, Atlassian Confluence, Atlassian JIRA, Tealium, Quality Assurance, Cross Browser Compatability, Image Optimization, Microsoft: Access, Word, Powerpoint, Excel

Work Experience

Marketing Front End Developer, Fisher Investments — Camas, WA

Oct 2016 — Present

- Oversee design, development, and data integrity of all global marketing lead gen landing page campaigns while preserving cross browser compatibility and mobile optimization
- Reduced speed-to-market time of a single campaign from three weeks to two days
- Collaborate with third party vendor teams on quality assurance of Sitecore CMS platform development to ensure bug free front end flexability/environment with in-depth testing
- Migrated and rebuilt 12 different country corporate websites to updated Sitecore CMS platform
- Defined internal JIRA workflow to adhere to business and legal requirements while maintaining documentation on all process flows

Web Content Specialist, Wacom Technology Corp. — Portland, OR

Jul 2016 — Oct 2016

- Integrated, edited, and proofread web content while maintaing existing templates with style guidelines in .com with Sitecore CMS platform and e-commerce platform Insite
- Partnered with UX designers to create user-friendly and attractive web pages

Web Development Intern, Mash LLC — Portland, OR

Jun 2016 — Jul 2016

 Developed and converted interface designs from desktop and mobile Sketch mock-ups to live code of an interactive game of Tic, Tac, Toe for internship project

Education

Web Development, Epicodus — Portland, OR Bachelor of Arts, Asia Studies, University of Washington — Seattle, WA Associate's of Arts, Japanese Language, Lewis and Clark College — Vancouver, WA 2016

2012

2010